## Leya Salazar Romero

Web Designer & Front-End Developer leyasalazar.com leyasalazarromero@gmail.com +18622878979





#### **Profile**

Creative and meticulous Web designer and Front-end developer graduated with the Web Design and Front-End Development A.A.S. degree and Graphic Design Certificate from Minneapolis College. Experience designing functional, aesthetically pleasing and inspiring works with a background in photography, mural art and digital art.

# **Experience**

## Freelance Graphic Designer - Illustrator, July, 2021 - Present

- Organization and creation of designs
- T-shirts, decals and stickers production

## Content Creator, @soyperuana.pe, November, 2021 - Present

- Design one weekly post for the instagram account with more than 15k followers.
- · Work within established brand identity guidelines

#### Front-End Developer, MPLS Design Show, 2021

- Work with peers to create a website in order to promote the work of graduating students
- Primarily use bootstrap programming language
- Utilize effective teamwork and communication skills in order to be a contributing teammate

http://www.mplscollegedesignshow.com/

## Web Designer and Front-End Developer, MPLS Apparel Portfolio, 2021

- Utilize the MS Teams platform to communicate with peers to build a website highlighting apparel graduating students
- Utilize bootstrap programming language to create the website
- Collaborate with moodboard ideas and designing concepts https://mcappareltechnologies.com

### **Education**

#### Minneapolis College

Minneapolis, MN 2018 - 2021

Associate of Applied Science Web Design and Front-End Development

Certificate, 30 Credits

Graphic Design: Print and Digital Media

#### **Skills**

- Languages: Spanish, English
- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, JQuery
- Adobe Creative Cloud (Illustrator, Xd, InDesign, Photoshop, Lightroom)
- Figma, Axure RP
- Visual Studio Code, WebStorm
- Trello, Notion, Slack
- Wiregraming
- Problem-solving
- Customer Service
- Adaptability
- Collaboration